I get at least one comment every day
asking how to mix your Zantham gum into
your Ninja Creamy. So, I'm going to show
you how to do it. It's actually much
simpler than you think. Let me show you
the hack. Starting off, you need some
liquid in your pint. So, we're using 400
g of fat-free high protein milk. And
[music] then you can set your pint to
the side and grab just a normal cup or
little dish. We're going to tear the
scale. And then you're going to add your
dry ingredients. We're going to add all
the dry ingredients. And this way you
can mix them up before adding them into
the milk. And then the zantham gum won't
clump up at all. So [music] watch this.
40 to 45 g of lacanto sweetener. Then
we're going to go in with our zantham
gum. Use about a/4 teaspoon. You can
also do this with the scale. Since it's
already at 42, it's going to be more
sensitive. So if you want to just add it
until it hits 43.1,
that'll be 1 g. If you tear it and then
try to add the zanthan gum, it probably
won't register. Just a little bit of
[music] salt, 1/ eighth of a teaspoon
maybe. And that's all the dry
ingredients. So that's what we're going
to be shaking up. Literally just swirl
it around for 2 3 seconds and then it's
ready to go in. So everything's
measured. We can put the scale away.
Bring back our pint. And then you can
just dump your dry ingredients [music]
into your wet. Now this won't clump up
at all. It'll be super easy to mix. The
zantham gum gets dispersed throughout
all the other dry ingredients. So it's
just mixes in way better. So, you
[music] can use a hand frothther like
this. I've kind of stopped using these
because they're not as effective. I
moved on to the immersion blender
because you can do it straight in the
pint. It won't scratch up the sides
because the blade is protected by the
walls of the immersion blender and
[music] it mixes way better. Especially
when you're mixing thicker ingredients
like nut butters, fruit, anything like
that. You can literally [music] just
blend it straight in the pint. So, it's
super helpful, super convenient, and the
most efficient way to do it. I forgot
the freaking vanilla bean paste. The
most important part. This is a vanilla
base if you're wondering.
>> Really only takes 30 to 60 seconds. Then
you have a perfectly blended pint, no
matter the flavor or ingredients. That's
how you mix in the zantham gum and the
best way to blend a ninja creamy in my
opinion.
Save this for making your next ninja
creamy. Send it to someone who might
find it helpful and follow for more tips
and tricks.